New York State Federation of Home Bureaus Records.
New York State Federation of Home Bureaus Records
- New York State Nutrition Committees - 1940s - Minutes, Memos, Flyers, Reports, Photographs
  - Nutrition Committee: Nutrition Fortnight - Radio Sub-Comm, 1941-1942 (Box 5)
  - School Lunch Program, 1941-1942; 1948-1949 (Box 5)
  - State Financial Aid, 1941-1949 (Box 5)
  - Emergency Welfare Services, 1942 (Box 5)
  - Mass Feeding: A War Measure, 1941-1942 (Box 5)
  - Nutrition Committee: Constitution and By-Laws, 1943-1944 (Box 5)
  - Nutrition Committee Resolutions (Box 5)
  - Committee Leadership Lists, 1946-1951 (Box 5)
  - Reports, 1940-1942 (Box 5)
  - Misc. Reports: Undated (Box 5)
  - Industrial Nutrition, 1950 (Box 5)
  - County Lists, 1940-1950 (Box 5)
  - County Lists: Undated (Box 5)
  - Miscellaneous and Undated Material, 1940 (Box 5)
  - Articles, Pamphlets, and Photographs (Box 5)
  - County Circulars, 1941 (Box 5)
  - County Circulars, 1942 (Box 5)
  - County Circulars, 1943 (Box 5)
  - County Circulars, 1943 (Box 5)
  - County Circulars, 1944 (Box 5)
  - County Circulars, 1945 (Box 5)
  - County Circulars, 1946 (Box 5)
  - County Circulars, 1947 (Box 5)
  - County Circulars, 1948 (Box 5)
  - Regional Meetings, 1941-1949 (Box 5)
  - County Committee Reports, 1940-1941 (Box 5)
  - Miscellaneous: Undated (Box 5)
  - Slides, 1960-1969 (Box 6)
- Press Services
  - News clippings from the start of the Home Bureau to 1957 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Programs, press releases on winners, show script of State Dress Revue, 1946-1949 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Press releases of Training School in Home Ec., 1944-1946 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Report and publicity aids, 1948-1949 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Press releases and bios of the club winners, 1946-1948 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Press releases and program of Extension Annual Conference, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Press Service - Facts for Fillers, Homemaker's Dispatch, News Releases, 1955 (Box 7)
  - Press Service - Facts for Fillers, Homemaker's Dispatch, News Releases, 1956 (Box 7)
  - Press Service - Facts for Fillers, Homemaker's Dispatch, News Releases, 1957 (Box 7)
  - Press Service - Facts for Fillers, Find the Fact, Homemaker's Dispatch, News Releases, 1958 (Box 7)
  - Press Service - Facts for Fillers, Find the Fact, Homemaker's Dispatch, News Releases, 1959 (Box 7)
  - Press Service - Facts for Fillers, Find the Fact, Homemaker's Dispatch, News Releases, 1960 (Box 7)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1950-1959 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Extension Service Annual Conference Program
  - Extension Service Conference, 1935 (Box 8)
  - Extension Service Conference, 1936 (Box 8)
  - Extension Service Conference, 1937 (Box 8)
  - Extension Service Conference, 1938 (Box 8)
  - Extension Service Conference, 1939 (Box 8)
  - Extension Service Conference, 1941 (Box 8)
- National Study - Women Enrolled in Home Demonstration Work
  - Cayuga County - Responses to Free-Answer Questions Tables, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Delaware County - Responses to Free-Answer Questions Tables, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Franklin County - Responses to Free-Answer Questions Tables, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Monroe County - Responses to Free-Answer Questions Tables, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Niagara County - Responses to Free-Answer Questions Tables, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Orange County - Responses to Free-Answer Questions Tables, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Rochester City -Responses to Free-Answer Questions Tables, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - St. Lawrence County - Responses to Free-Answer Questions Tables, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Suffolk County - Responses to Free-Answer Questions Tables, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Wyoming County - Responses to Free-Answer Questions Tables, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Reports and Publications
  - Federation Newsletter, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Health Newsletter, 1937-1939 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Health Newsletter, 1939-1942 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - New York State Extension Service in Home Economics (17 volumes), 1918-1936 (Box 10)
  - New York State Extension Service in Home Economics (15 volumes), 1937-1952 (Box 11)
  - New York State Extension Service in Home Economics (6 volumes), 1953-1958 (Box 12)
  - Annual Report New York State Extension Service in Home Economics (5 volumes), 1959-1963 (Box 12)
  - Annual Report New York State Extension Service in Home Economics (2 volumes), 1964-1965 (Box 13)
  - Cooperative Extension New York Home Economics Annual Report (6 volumes), 1966-1971 (Box 13)
  - Annual Reports, 1972-1977 (Box 14)
  - Membership Study - State Summary, 1958 (Box 14)
  - Cornell Cooperative Extension Human Ecology - Program Resources, 1988-1991 (Box 14)
  - Noble, L.A. - M.S. - (A Study of Training Needs of Home Demonstration Agents in New York), 1959 (Box 14)
  - Home Bureau Federation News; Handbook 1953,1954; Scholarships Brochure, 1951-1956 (Box 15, Folder 6)